# LEANDERSON DIAS DE LIMA

#### +5511940139899

leanderson.devlima@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

BackEnd developer from Barueri, Brazil, with experience in **C#** and **.Net**, with proficiency in **SQL**, **Entity Framework** and Front End integration (HTML, CSS and JavaScript). Experience in projects with communication in **English**. Currently studying **Software Engineering**. Practical in technologies such as **GIT**, **Database**. Growing skills in **Ruby**, **C#** and **Python**.

#### **SKILLS**

- Cloud AWS
- C#
- .NET Framework
- ASP.NET MVC
- SQL
- GIT
- JavaScript/CSS/Html
- Python
- Ruby

## **LANGUAGES**

- Portuguese (Native)
- English (Advanced)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

DevOps Engineer - Criadigi | São Paulo, Brazil

\*April 2024 - Present

- Monitoring of Cloudflare indicators, including analysis of access IPs, detection of suspicious activities, and blocking of malicious IPs.
- Deployment of projects on AWS, configuration of services such as Amazon EC2, Amazon WorkMail, Amazon SES, Route 53, DNS, and issuance of HTTPS certificates.
- Collaboration with internal teams to ensure site security and performance.

Developer - Didox Business & Technology | São Paulo, Brazil

November 2023 - December 2023

- Layout development using React and Next.js.
- Efficient integration with the API via Swagger.
- Close collaboration with the backend team in C# and .NET.

• Effective communication with clients and maintenance of technical documentation.

## Developer - Wipro | Curitiba, Brazil

June 2022 - June 2023

- Administration and deployment of C# Asp .NET Framework application.
- Monitoring and organization of scripts.
- Knowledge base update.
- English communication in report meetings.

# Quality Assurance (QA) Test Analyst - Keeggo | São Paulo, Brazil

January 2022 - June 2022

- BITS MAP analysis according to ISO 8583.
- Execution and creation of tests.
- Technical and functional specifications.
- Creation and analysis of test cases.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor's Degree | Software Engineering**

Univesp, São Paulo, Brazil

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Decola Tech .NET	Future Code Training in .Net and Angular
Pottencial .NET Developer	Algorithm
.NET Developer Formation	GFT Quality Assurance #1
Ruby Developer Formation	QA TRIP (Python Testing)
Cloud Solutions	Full Stack Web Programming

# LINKEDIN

• LinkedIn

## **PORTFOLIO**

- GitHub LeanLima7
- GitHub LeanDevLima
- GitLab LeanDevLima